

# Angel Guillermo Montaña

## Full Stack Developer

#### About me

From an early age I have been passionate about technology, my life experiences led me to lead work groups, I would be pleased to capture those experiences and personal relationships in the IT area. I am always in constant search of new goals and challenges to expand my knowledge.





- San Juan, Argentina
- in linkedin.com/in/angel-guillermo-montaña
- g<u>ithub.com/AngelGuillermo</u> <u>Montania</u>

## Skills

#### Tech:

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | TypeScript | NPM | ReactJs | React-Native | NextJs |
Redux | Figma | Bootstrap | TailwindCSS | NodeJs | Postman |
ExpressJs | APIs | Sequelize | NestJs | MVC |
PostgreSQL | MySQL | GIT | Github | Babel | WebPack | JestJS

#### Soft:

Scrum | Conflict resolution | Teamwork |
Good communication | Pro-activity | Autonomous Learning

## **Academic experience**

#### Full Stack Developer

<u>Inmuebles (Required group project for Henry)</u>

Mar.2022 - April.2022

- Web application for the sale, purchase or rental of real estate internationally. Able to manage and guarantee appointments between users.
- Technologies and methodologies used: React-Redux, Redux-Thunk, Tailwind, Sequelize, AWS (Service S3), Auth0, ExpressJs, PostgreSQL, API, NodeJs, NodeMailer, Git, GitHub, Scrum.

## Full Stack Developer

<u>Slow Motion (Required group project for DigitalHouse)</u>

Aug.2021 - Mar.2022

- Creation and development of web application to buy and rent, movies and series by a user. Using different libraries, it is able to manage products and users.
- Technologies and methodologies used: Figma, EJS, CSS3, MVC, ExpressJs, NodeJs, Git, GitHub, MySQL, Sequelize, Scrum, Multer, API

### <u>Full Stack Developer</u>

Pokemon Api (Required individual project for Henry)

Jan.2022

- Creation and development of a web application capable of consuming an API, working together with Sequelize it is possible to execute the corresponding CRUD of pokemons.
- Technologies used: React-Redux, Css-modules, Sequelize, Express, PostgreSQL, Node, Git, GitHub.

## Education

2022 - In Progress	Web programming Oracle Next Education (Alura)
2021-2022	Web programming, Full Stack Henry
2021-2022	Web programming, Full Stack Digital House
2013-2015	Cisco Network Specialist - CCNA2 Approved ISRI (Instituto Superior de Redes e Informática)
2011-2013	PC repair and maintenance ISRI (Instituto Superior de Redes e Informática)

## **Experiences**

Front end development teacher ADA ITW 2022

Site manager Busso Construcciones 2019 - 2021

- Hygiene and safety practices. Calculate, execute and design in AutoCad software
- Divide, plan and execute tasks necessary for the building.
- Ensure a correct work environment.

PC repair technician Independent 2014 - 2021